<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:isDelivered="{Boolean}false"
        cq:template="/libs/core/franklin/templates/page"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="conference"
        sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/page/v1/page"
        pageTitle="Conference - adaptTo() 2024"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:ReplicationStatus]"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2024-04-30T00:00:00.000+02:00"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/root/v1/root">
            <section
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/section/v1/section">
                <text
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/text/v1/text"
                    text="&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot; data-section-status=&quot;loaded&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&quot;default-content-wrapper&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&quot;about-adaptto&quot;&gt;About adaptTo()&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2011 pro!vision GmbH, an expert for web content management with AEM, started adaptTo() as a Berlin-based &amp;bdquo;Apache Sling &amp;amp; Friends Tech Meetup&amp;rdquo;. Since then, many helping hands, dedicated sponsors, top-notch speakers and an enthusiastic developer community have contributed to the conference becoming what it is today: Europe&amp;rsquo;s leading AEM Developer Conference.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;pro!vision became part of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.diva-e.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;diva-e&lt;/a&gt; in 2020, one of Germany&amp;rsquo;s leading digital service providers. With more than 20 years of experience in digital business and more than 100 Adobe experts, diva-e fully covers the digital value chain from strategy to technology to creation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;diva-e has now become the official organizer and host of the adaptTo().&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-idea-behind-adaptto&quot;&gt;The idea behind adaptTo()&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;adaptTo() is a conference from developers for developers&lt;/strong&gt;. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for promising roll-ups, brimming swag bags and glittering product presentations, this event isn&amp;rsquo;t for you. We&amp;rsquo;re talking about a highly specialized developer conference with a clear focus on technology which is on &lt;a href=&quot;https://business.adobe.com/products/experience-manager/adobe-experience-manager.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Adobe Experience Manager (AEM)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://business.adobe.com/products/adobe-experience-cloud-products.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Adobe Experience Cloud (AEC)&lt;/a&gt;, and underlying open source software such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://sling.apache.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Apache Sling&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://felix.apache.org/documentation/index.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Apache Felix&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://jackrabbit.apache.org/oak/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Apache Jackrabbit Oak&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://wcm.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;wcm.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;adaptTo() is a conference of experts&lt;/strong&gt; with a clear objective: Bringing together the best AEM developers and OSS enthusiasts from all over the world &amp;ndash; and inviting the best in their field to share the knowledge with the participants. Those who speak at adaptTo() do not talk about themselves, but much rather about their work which makes sure all attendees get unadulterated and far-reaching insights into the thinking and doing of real experts and experienced practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;adaptTo() is a conference with community flair&lt;/strong&gt;. It has its origins in a developer community that loves and lives the exchange of knowledge and experience. This means we make sure the conference offers all participants enough space and time for discussions and networking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-you-should-attend&quot;&gt;Why you should attend&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get insights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how experienced you are in your field, there is always room to grow. At adaptTo() you gain valuable insights by enthusiast speakers, passionate practitioners or by the audience&amp;rsquo;s questions and perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get connected&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;adaptTo() is the perfect opportunity to get yourself connected to experienced developers from all over Europe, that share your interest in Adobe Experience Manager (AEM) and Open Source Software (OSS). In addition to the lectures, there will be lots of space and opportunities to network or to deepen existing contacts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get away&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We all love the work we do (at least most of us do), but from time to time we all need a break from our daily grind and routines. So why not take the chance to get away for a few days and visit Europe's leading AEM developer conference in one of Europe's most exciting cities. And tell your boss to not worry. It's not all about fun. Your trip will be productive.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a t-shirt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, besides all the valuable insights you also get an attendee shirt.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&quot;ticket-prices&quot;&gt;Ticket Prices&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Early bird ticket (till June 30th): 849&amp;euro;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Early bird group ticket (till June 30th, min. 5): 779&amp;euro;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loyalty price for Visitors of recent adaptTo() Conferences (till August 31st): 789&amp;euro;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular ticket: 939&amp;euro;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Regular group ticket (min. 5): 859&amp;euro;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Special price for Apache Committers: 329&amp;euro;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All prices including tax.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you qualify for a loyalty ticket or as Apache Committer please send us an &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:info@adapt.to&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;e-mail&lt;/a&gt; for getting the discount code. &lt;a href=&quot;https://adapt.to/2024/sign-up/call-for-papers&quot;&gt;Speakers&lt;/a&gt; attend for free.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cancellation policy&lt;/strong&gt;: Ticket can be canceled until Oct. 4th 2024. We will refund the ticket price, but have to charge you with 5% of the ticket price. You can always transfer a ticket to someone else. From October 5th on it's no longer possible to cancel a ticket.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any questions? Our conference team is happy to help: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:info@adapt.to&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;info@adapt.to&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;"/>
            </section>
        </root>
        <image jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
